你怎么贴了个邦迪
Why are you wearing a Band-Aid?
哈雷咬我
Halley bit me.
你被女生给虐了
You got beaten up by a girl.
你这是性别歧视
Hey, that's sexist.
你说得对
You're right.
你被小婴儿给虐啦
You got beaten up by a baby.
你手上拿的什么呢
What you got there?
我在前面小摊子买的三明治
Oh, I grabbed a sandwich at the food truck out front.
等等  姑娘请留步
Wait, n-now, hold on.
今晚是周五夜
Tonight is Friday,
我想你应该知道这代表什么
and I believe you know what that means.
我有趣年轻的生命突然要急转直下吗
That my fun, young life took a drastic turn somewhere?
不是
No.
其实说对了
But yeah.
意思是今晚是中餐夜
No, that means it's Chinese food night.
是啊  你也叫了中餐  快吃吧
Yeah, and you have Chinese food. So eat it.
但我能闻到你的熏牛肉
But I can smell your pastrami.
我们也都听得到你的抱怨声
And we can all hear your complaining,
谁都不高兴  很公平啊
so no one's happy.
的确闻起来很好吃
It does smell good.
是的  我那天也吃了一份
Oh, it is. I had one the other day.
这是在干嘛
What is happening?
大家现在应该是要吃中餐
Everybody's supposed to be eating Chinese food.
其实呢  我相信三明治
Well, actually, I believe the Chinese
有可能是中国人发明的呢
may have invented the sandwich.
他们的"肉夹馍"字面意思就是
Their dish "Rou jia mo" literally means
"肉夹在面包里"
"Meat between bread."
所以我们所有人  包含佩妮
So, it looks like all of us, including Penny,
都在吃中餐啊
are eating Chinese food.
除了你  谢尔顿  你在吃瘪[乌鸦]
Except for you, Sheldon. You're eating crow.
抱歉  我觉得你忘了
I'm sorry, I think you're forgetting
三明治是由
that the sandwich was invented
三明治伯爵约翰·孟塔古所发明的
by John Montagu, the Earl of Sandwich.
小摊的名字叫"三明治[地名]之珠"
Oh. The truck's called "Pearl of Sandwich."
我现在懂这哏了
Now I get it.
好了  这味道太香了  我也要去买一份
All right, that smells too good. I got to get one of those.
但我觉得你忘了中国的面包夹肉
And I think you're forgetting that there are written documents
在唐代的文献上就有记载来证明了
of meat between bread being eaten in China during the Tang dynasty.
这样吧  我跟你去买
You know what, I'll go with you.
或许我们能直接开溜回家
And then maybe we just go home.
我觉得你对面包的定义很宽松啊
I think you're defining bread very loosely.
如果这样的话  何时才能结束
If we go down that road, where does it end?
我本来想回答到我们睡觉就能结束
Well, I would say when we go to bed,
但你睡觉还说梦话
but you talk in your sleep.
我不想现在跟你继续辩下去
I don't want to get into this with you right now.
等我睡觉之后我们再谈
We'll talk about this when I'm asleep.
我不想等你睡着后才谈
I don't want to talk about it when you're asleep.
我们为什么不能现在谈
How come we can't talk about it now?
因为我现在在吃东西啊
Well, because I'm eating now.
行行行  那你的木须肉如何
Fine. How's your moo shu?
其实还挺不错的
You know what? It's great.
等等  你瞧瞧
Wait, look at that.
或许三明治还真是中国人发明的
Hmm. Well, maybe the Chinese did invent the sandwich.
看来你刚才说的是对的
I guess you were right.
可惜没人在旁见证这一刻
Too bad no one's around to hear it.
第十一季  第十九集
我在楼上都能闻到楼下小摊的味道
I can smell that food truck from up here.
如果你不喜欢那味道你就关窗啊
Just close the window if you don't like the smell.
我当然喜欢那味道啊
Of course I like the smell.
就是盐巴跟油脂
It's salt and fat.
我的大脑已经进化完毕  但我的舌头还是想
My brain may be evolved, but my tongue still wants
捡起一根木棒  把那小摊敲晕再拖回我的山洞
to pick up a club and drag that truck back to my cave.
所以有一个你很喜欢
So, there's something you like,
但是也快把你给逼疯的东西
but it's also driving you crazy.
我有经验  正在体验中
Been there, doing it now.
这太令人分心了
No, it-it's a distraction.
这样我怎么专心工作啊
How can I focus on my work
我满脑子都在想着我有多想吃那三明治
when all I can think about is how much I want that sandwich?
那你就去买一个吃啊
So, go get one.
我不能一有冲动就对自己妥协啊
I can't just give in to every urge I have when I have it.
这就是为什么我必须按表操课
That's why I have a rigid schedule.
我没克制住冲动  做了一个严格的时间表
It's bad enough I had to give in to my urge
就已经够堕落了
to create a rigid schedule.
这样吧  要不我们下楼去找那小摊
You know, why don't I just go down to the food truck
请求他们换个地方卖
and ask them to move?
-那你为什么还带上现金了  -不为什么
- Why are you taking cash? - No reason.
人生就是得这样
Oh, this is the life.
还有什么比这个更好的呢
What could be better than this?
比如你不是穿着我的泳裤就更好了
If you weren't wearing one of my swimsuits.
我会还给你的
I'll give it back.
你懂规矩
You know the rule--
碰过小鸡鸡  就被我抛弃
once it touches hiney, it's no longer miney.
你要不要这么死心眼
You're such a prude.
你知道这水现在正"碰"着哪些东西吗
Do you know all the things this water's touching right now?
我放松完了
Well, I'm relaxed enough.
霍华德  你看
Hey, Howard, look.
那是什么
What's that?
感觉像是别人的无人机
Looks like someone's drone.
惨了
Oh, no.
会不会是有人在偷看我们泡澡啊
Do you think it was spying on us in the hot tub?
人家离可去海滩见人的身材还差了6成
'Cause I'm only 40% of the way to my beach bod.
其中一个螺旋桨坏了
One of the propellers is broken.
这是坠机在这里的
It must have crashed.
你觉得你能修好吗
Oh. Do you think you could fix it?
或许吧  但我们是不是该先找到主人是谁
Maybe. Should we try and track down the owner first?
这样应该比较好
Yeah, that's probably a good idea.
有人弄丢无人机了吗
Anyone lose a drone?
看来这是我们的了
Looks like it's ours.
太好啦  我们有无人机啦
Yay, we got a drone!
Oh. Yay, we got a drone.
熏牛肉小摊换地方了
The pastrami truck moved.
带轮子的餐厅就会有这种危险
That is the danger of a restaurant on wheels.
不是  好像是有人去跟居委会投诉了
No, apparently someone complained to the tenants association,
现在那小摊不允许在我们这条街摆摊了
and they're not allowed to park on our street anymore.
谁会去投诉一个所有人都爱的东西啊
Who would complain about something that everyone loves?
你去跟居委会投诉小摊了吗
Did you complain to the tenants association about the food truck?
是的
Yes.
他们居然把你的话当一回事了吗
And they actually took you seriously?
居委会把所有的投诉都很当一回事
Oh, the tenants association takes every complaint seriously.
那就最好了  因为我要给他们发电邮
Oh, great, because I'm about to send them an e-mail
来投诉你这个人
complaining about you.
抱歉
Excuse me.
某人发信前应该先做拼字检查啊
Someone should have spell-checked.
这是怎么一回事
What is going on here?
你就是居委会吗
You're the tenants association?
你真应该看看你现在脸上的表情
You should see the look on your face.
或许你会想告诉你夫人
You might want to tell your wife
熏牛肉的"熏"没有"艹"字头
that there's no "y" in "pastrami."
这样应该就行了
Okay, that ought to do it.
我把坏的螺旋桨给换了
I've replaced the propeller
并重新装上了平衡环控制单元
and reattached the gimbal controller unit.
兄弟  你就像专治机器人的《实习医生格蕾》啊
Dude, you're like Grey's Anatomy for robots.
还有  这怎么还没做成节目呢
Also, why isn't that a show?
现在看看我能不能
I just need to see if I can re-sync
把它跟这个旧控制器同步到一起
the controls to this old remote.
我们应该取个名
We should name it.
无人机还是你的白痴机器人节目
The drone, or your stupid robot show?
无人机
The drone.
那个节目已经有名字了
The show's already got a name--
《综合医院》是一部知名的长寿美国日间医学电视剧
《综合机院》
General Bot-spital.
我弄好它啦
I got it working! ?
我们来玩威廉·退尔吧
Let's play William Tell.
农民威廉·退尔当年因事受罚  总督要他射中放在他儿子脑袋上的苹果才释放他们
我把碗放在我头上
I'll put this bowl on my head.
看你能不能不碰到我就把它打下去
See if you can knock it off without hitting me.
你就是我肚子里的蛔虫啊
You read my mind.
你们在干嘛啊
What are you doing?
不是打破一个碗  就是打破拉杰脑袋
Either breaking a bowl or breaking Raj's head.
你小心点  那碗已经停产了
Be careful, they don't make that bowl anymore.
是一台好无人机呢
It's a nice one.
对啊  我们在院子里发现  把它修好了
Yeah. We found it in the yard and fixed it up.
你不担心外面有个孩子
Aren't you worried there's some kid out there
正在找他的无人机吗
missing his drone?
拜托  伯纳黛特
Oh, please, Bernadette,
这不是小孩的玩具好吗
this is not a children's toy, okay?
这上面有高清摄像头呢
This thing's got an HD camera on it.
好吧  所以你不担心外面有个
Okay, then aren't you worried there's some rich
有钱的偷窥狂正在找他的无人机吗
peeping tom out there missing his drone?
我们问过了  没人来认领啊
We asked around, and no one claimed it.
我觉得我们已经尽力了
Ha. I think we've done all we can do.
你检查记忆卡了吗
Did you check the video card?
也许能看到它是从哪里起飞的呢
Maybe you can see where it started off from.
真是个好主意啊  亲爱的
What a great idea, honey.
让我把事情搞清楚
So, let me get this straight.
你是居委会主席吗
You are the president of the tenants association?
主席  唯一成员  最严厉的批评家
President, only member, and harshest critic.
我曾经就自己边洗澡边开会
I once gave myself an official reprimand
给了自己一个官方的谴责
for conducting a meeting in the shower.
蒸汽把我的木槌弄弯了
The steam warped my gavel.
所以上次我把衣服留在烘干机太久
Okay, so when I got a fine for leaving my clothes
收到了一张罚单  那是你开的吗
in the dryer for too long, that was from you?
14.99元
$14.99.
正是购买新木槌的价格
The exact price of a new gavel.
还有我们给为你唱生日快乐歌
And the noise complaint we got
收到的扰民警告呢
for singing you "Happy Birthday"?
从朋友角度来看  我倍受感动
As a friend, I was touched.
但身为本大楼的代表
As a representative of the building,
我觉得你们唱得都找不到调了
I thought that you should pick a key and stick with it.
你知道这家伙是整个居委会吗
Do you know he is the entire tenants association?
不知道  但我不意外
No, but I'm not surprised.
他还是自己在超空间发明的星球上的教皇呢
He's also the pope of a planet he invented in hyperspace.
你为什么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me?
因为我想确定你爱的是我本人
'Cause I wanted to make sure that you loved the man,
而不是权力
not the office.
你不能凭个人意愿就当主席
You can't just declare yourself president.
我没有  我召开了会议
I didn't. I called a meeting,
只有我自己参加
I was the only one to attend.
我提名了自己  经过一番动人的演讲
I nominated myself, and after a pretty moving speech,
我选了自己
I voted myself in.
如果你可以选你自己
Well, if you can vote yourself in,
-那我们就把你罢免  -对
- then we can vote you out. - Yeah.
-行  请在下次开会时提出动议  -什么时候
- Fine. Make a motion at the next meeting. - When is that?
每个月的第一个周六
It's the first Saturday of every month.
除非有召开紧急会议
Unless there's an emergency meeting.
那我们就开紧急会议
Then we call an emergency meeting.
你真不需要这么做
You really don't have to.
今天就是本月的第一个周六
This is the first Saturday of the month.
好吧  那我们要把你罢免
Okay, fine. Then we vote you out.
等一等
Uh, uh, hold on.
等等  首先
Hold on. First,
我们先得读上个月的会议记录
we have to read the minutes from last month's meeting.
艾米  能劳烦你一下吗
Amy, would you do the honors?
好吧
Why not?
"周六  3月3号
"Saturday, March 3rd.
7点5分  开会
0705, meeting called to order.
7点6分  主席的眼睛里沾了洗发水
0706, president gets shampoo in eye.
7点7分  散会"
0707, meeting adjourned."
我们可以罢免你了吧
Okay, can we vote you out now?
很好  新事宜
Ah, very well. New business.
我提出对现任主席
I move for a vote of no confidence
-不信任的提案   -没错
- in the president. - Yeah.
2比1  你输了
Two to one, you lose.
别急  我们还有一位租客
Not so fast. I believe we have one tenant here
没有发言呢
who has not made her voice heard.
我们在等你呢  未婚妻
We're waiting, fiancee.
没错  我们在等你  好闺蜜
Yeah, we're waiting, best friend.
我们在等你
Yeah, we're waiting,
上次需要电池时
neighbor who needed a battery
从我这里无条件获得一节的邻居
and totally got one from me, no strings attached.
我不想掺和你们的事
I don't want to be in the middle of this.
不管我怎么选
No matter which way I vote, I'm either
我就会变成一个坏闺蜜  坏未婚妻
a bad friend, a bad fiancee,
或者是拿了电池不知恩图报的坏人
or an ungrateful recipient of a battery.
下一次我在浴室开会时
Next time I have a meeting in the shower,
欢迎你来参加
you're welcome to attend.
谢尔顿  谢尔顿主席  我选谢尔顿
Sheldon. Sheldon for president. I pick Sheldon!
不敢相信我最好的朋友站了谢尔顿队
Ugh, I can't believe my best friend sided with Sheldon.
不敢相信我最好的朋友就是谢尔顿
Can't believe my best friend is Sheldon.
我应该抢过他的木槌
Ah, I should've taken that gavel
从他的喉咙插下去
and shoved it right down this throat.
我会从另一个洞插进去
I would've gone the other way,
不过终点也会插到喉咙
but it would've gotten to his throat.
怎么了
What?
别生我的气
Don't be mad at me.
我不能投他的反对票呀
I mean, I can't vote against him.
哪怕他是在耍疯吗
Even when he's being crazy?
难道他有不疯的时候吗
Well, what other times are there?!
那你就放任他随心所欲乱来吗
So you just let him get away with anything?
也不是随心所欲啦
Well, not anything.
不过老实说  我也不想死在
But honestly, pastrami sandwich
熏牛肉三明治这座山上
is not the hill I want to die on.
这不仅仅是三明治
It's not about the sandwich.
而是原则问题
It's about the principle.
对  原则问题
Yeah, principle.
-三明治也有点关系  -对
- And a little bit sandwich. - Yeah.
这楼里还有不少租客
Look, there are a bunch of other tenants in this building.
你只需要再拉一个人投你们就行了
All you need is for one of them to vote your way,
这样谢尔顿被罢免  我也不用背叛他
and then Sheldon's out and I didn't betray him.
这个主意倒是不错
Hey, you know, that's actually a good plan.
这主意是你们自己想出来的  不关我事
That you came up with all by yourself.
现在  请原谅我
Now, if you'll excuse me,
我告诉谢尔顿出来逛超市了
told Sheldon I was going to the market,
所以  我得拿点你们的东西走
so... I'm taking some of your stuff.
我从没来过你们家
I was never here.
有时候她在谢尔顿旁所以不容易发现
Sometimes you don't see it 'cause she's next to Sheldon,
但其实她也是个怪人啊
but she's pretty weird.
好吧  都连上了  开始吧
Okay. All hooked up. Here we go.
我希望里面没什么恶心人的东西
I hope there's nothing disturbing on there.
比如你俩一起泡澡吗
Like you two in a hot tub?
等等  有图像出来了
Hold on. Now I'm getting a picture.
光这点也没戏唱啊
That's not very much to go on.
光这点戏就可多了
Oh, that's plenty to go on.
我们不能放弃
We can't give up.
我们一定得找到她
We got to find her.
你只是因为她可爱才想找到她
You just want to find her 'cause she's cute.
不光是因为她可爱
Not just because she's cute.
她还拥有一架昂贵的无人机
She also owns a pretty expensive drone,
表示她有钱还爱乱花
which means she has money and doesn't mind wasting it.
而哥...  就爱这样的女人
And I... I like that in a woman.
你有看到任何可以找到她的线索吗
Do you see anything that could help us locate her?
让我仔细看看
Hmm, let me have a look.
她可有一双鹰眼
She's got eagle eyes,
总能在电影中发现连续性错误
always spotting continuity errors in movies.
一点都不烦人
It's not annoying at all.
那里
Oh. There.
就在那里
Right there.
看看她衣服上的别针
Check out the pin on her jacket.
这不是漫画店的吗
Isn't that from the comic book store?
是吗
Hmm, is it?
霍华德  放大
Hey, Howard, zoom in. Oh.
好吧  放大
Fine. Zooming in.
我知道你就是在耍贱
Yeah, I know you're being a jerk,
但这招还真有效呢
but it's actually helpful.
你好
Hi.
你好  我们是你楼下的邻居
Hi. We're your neighbors from downstairs.
我们见过
We've met.
记得吗
Remember?
我邀请你们参加了我的乔迁派对
I invited you to my housewarming when I moved in.
对哦  抱歉
Oh, yeah. Sorry.
那个  最近这几个月我们都忙疯了
You know, it's been a crazy couple months.
那是两年前了
That was two years ago.
欢迎搬来这幢大楼
Welcome to the building. Mm-hmm.
我正在竞选居委会主席
So, I-I'm running for president of the tenants association.
希望你可以选我
I could really use your vote.
你说你们会来玩
You said you were gonna stop by.
人家还买了好多吃的
I bought a lot of food.
总之  会议就在明天
Anyway, meeting's tomorrow.
我们希望你能来参加
We really hope you can make it.
-我会来的  -真的吗
- I'll be there. - Oh, really?
真的  你们最好准备很多吃的
Yeah. You should buy a lot of food.
我正在竞选居委会主席
So, I'm running for president of the tenants association
希望你可以选我
and I could really use your vote.
那谁是现在的主席
Uh, who's president now?
谢尔顿·库珀
Uh, Sheldon Cooper.
就是那个这么高
You know, about yay tall
这么烦人的人
and about yay annoying.
所以你想让我反对谢尔顿·库珀吗
So you want me to vote against Sheldon Cooper?
没错  你只需要到会...
Yeah. You just need to show up at a meeting...
不行  我来不了
Oh, no, no. No can do.
他有对我的人身限制令
He's got a restraining order against me.
真的吗  为什么
Really? Why?
我有一次把他锁在楼顶上了
Uh, I locked him on the roof once.
其实是三次
Three times.
帕特里斯古太太
So, Mrs. Petrescu,
我们希望你能投给莱纳德
we were hoping you would vote for Leonard
而不是投给谢尔顿
instead of voting for Sheldon.
投给谢尔顿
Vote Sheldon.
不  投给莱纳德
No, no. Vote Leonard.
不投给莱纳德
No vote Leonard.
不  要投给莱纳德
No. Vote Leonard.
谢谢
Thank you.
她戴着你店里的别针
She's wearing a pin from your store.
你知道她是谁吗
Do you know who she is?
知道  这是辛西娅
Oh, sure, yeah. That's Cynthia.
所以她是客人
Wha... s-so, she's a customer?
没错  但我有一阵没见过她了
Yeah, yeah, but I-I haven't seen her in a while.
在你发表意见前
And before you say anything,
我强调下  女性不再来店里的原因很多
there is a lot of reasons women stop coming here.
不都是因为我
It's not just me.
但这次...
But this time...
是因为我
It was me. Yeah.
我当时在尝试新的撩妹笑容
I was trying out a flirty new smile.
我不常用到"食尸鬼般"这个词  但是
Now, I don't use the word "ghoulish" a lot, but...
我真的想不到别的词来形容你了
I-I just can't think of another word.
等等  你知道怎么找到她吗
Wait, do you know how to find her?
嗯  我应该有她的邮寄地址
Yeah. I think I have her address on my mailing list.
拜托  让我把无人机送还给她
Oh. Hey. Please, let me bring the drone back to her.
你觉得自己有机会吗
You think you've got a shot?
-万一她结婚了呢  -她没结婚
- What if she's married? - She's not.
这就是命中注定啦
It's meant to be.
奉劝你一句
A little tip.
使用你熟悉常用的笑容就好
Uh, stick with the smiles you know.
你在干嘛
Hi. What are you doing?
莱纳德和佩妮想让租客们反对我
Leonard and Penny are trying to turn the tenants against me,
他们即将见识到
so they are about to see just what kind of power
居委会主席所掌有的权力
the president of the tenants association wields.
"身高必须超过这里才能使用洗衣机"
"You must be at least this tall to use washing machine"?
我会挂在比莱纳德高的地方
I'm gonna hang it up higher than Leonard.
那他的衣服就会臭死了
And then his clothes will smell.
没人会投票给穿臭衣服的人
And nobody's voting for a man with smelly clothes.
毕竟另外一名候选人
No, not when there's a perfectly unscented
是毫无异味的现任主席
incumbent on the ballot.
谢尔顿  我手握研究人脑领域的高级学位
Sheldon, I have an advanced degree in the study of the human brain,
所以如果我未婚夫是个胡说八道的疯子
so if my fiancé is a raving lunatic,
对我的名声多少会造成影响
it's kind of a ding on my reputation.
如果领袖们
If leaders just stepped aside
每次遇到屁民的反对就让位
every time they didn't have the consent of the governed,
那我们会拥有什么
what would we have?
民主
Democracy.
有我在  想都别想
Not on my watch.
好  表现正常点
Okay. Don't be weird.
表现正常点  表现正常点
Don't be weird. Don't be weird.
你好
Hello.
你找到我的无人机了
Hey. You found my drone.
是的  没错
Yeah, yeah. Yes.
花了点时间才找到你
It took a while to track you down,
不过看到你惊喜的表情  都值了
but to see the look on your face, it was worth it.
你嘴真甜
Aw, that's sweet.
我是拉杰什
Rajesh.
-我是辛西娅  -很高兴认识你
- Cynthia. - Ah, pleasure to meet you.
我也是
Likewise.
我觉得应该给你些奖赏之类的
I-I feel like I should give you a reward or something.
不用了  没这必要
Oh, oh, no, you don't have to do that.
不  我坚持
No, I insist.
那给我你的电话号码怎么样
How about your phone number?
把你的手机给我
Give me your phone.
谢谢  我会打给你的  辛西娅
Thanks. So, I'll-I'll call you, Cynthia.
好的  拉杰什
Great, Rajesh.
再次感谢你
And thanks again.
不客气
Uh, sure.
小心驶得万年船
Just checking.
谢尔顿
Hey, Sheldon.
我们发现了很有意思的东西
We found something pretty interesting.
真是意外啊
Huh. Well, that is surprising.
我个人完全不知道他们在说什么
I, for one, have no idea what they're talking about.
原来当艾米租下佩妮的公寓时
Turns out, when Amy took over Penny's apartment,
租约上写的是她的名字  而不是你
she was put on the lease, not you.
对  而我搬到对面时
Yeah, and when I moved across the hall,
你的名字从租约去掉了  我的名字加上去了
you got taken off the lease and I got added.
什么意思
Well, what are you saying?
你是说谢尔顿严格来说并不是租户
That Sheldon's not technically a tenant at all
所以  无论谁投票给他
and therefore, has no standing to be president
他都没资格当居委会主席吗
of the tenants association no matter who votes for him?
我不知道你们是怎么找到这漏洞的
I don't know how you found that out,
但我猜应该是全靠你们自己
but I am guessing all on your own.
看来我们得想出
So, looks like we need to figure out
新主席应该让谁来当了
who the new president should be.
-我提名我自己  -我赞成
- I nominate myself. - I second it.
身为一个恋爱中的女人  我想支持我的男人
Well, as a woman in love, I want to stand by my man.
很可惜官僚主义抹杀了这个可能性
Too bad that's been rendered bureaucratically impossible.
这对我来说很艰难
Well, this is hard for me
因为我确实喜欢找到法律上的瑕疵
because I do love a legal technicality
而这个真心不错
and this is a good one.
不过  还是比不上加州法律的一条条款
Although, not quite as good as the provision in California law,
此条款声明  连续在同一寓所居住30天的人
which states a person who occupies a dwelling
自动成为任意承租人
for 30 consecutive days becomes a tenant at will
因此...
and as such...
-我投给莱纳德  -你...
- I vote for Leonard! - You...
什么
What?
对不起  谢尔顿
I'm sorry, Sheldon.
权力[能力]越低  责任越小
With minimal power comes minimal responsibility,
而且你根本做不好
and you couldn't handle it.
你别乱改《蜘蛛侠》里的名言
Don't you misquote Spider-Man to me.
不是你的错
It's not your fault.
谁会不被决定洗衣房
I mean, what man wouldn't be seduced
开到几点这种权力所诱惑呢
by the power to decide how late the laundry room stays open?
等等  就是你害我不得不第二天早上
Wait, you're the reason I had to come back
才去拿洗好的牛仔裤吗
and get my jeans the next morning?
真不敢相信你要我放弃这个
I can't believe you expect me to give that up.
谢尔顿  这是美国的方式
Sheldon, it's the American way,
和平的权力交接
the peaceful transfer of power.
是吗
I don't know.
想想蚁人
Think about Ant-Man.
我无时无刻不在想蚁人
I'm always thinking about Ant-Man.
皆为《蚁人》中的演员
迈克尔·道格拉斯把自己的战衣
Michael Douglas had the suit
传给了保罗·路德
and then he passed it on to Paul Rudd.
也许你说得对
Maybe you're right.
不是吧  蚁人的鬼话
Really? The Ant-Man thing?
你居然被这一套说服了
That's what won you over?
没错  因为他说对了细节
Yes. He got the details right.
这才是超级英雄的正常提及方式
That's how you use a superhero.
我想是时候把这个传给莱纳德了
I suppose it is time I passed this on to Leonard.
-谢谢你  -对  谢谢
- Thank you. - Yeah, thanks.
我知道这对你来说实属不易
I-I know that's hard for you.
的确
Well, it was.
但你知道吗
But you know what?
现在我不在位了
Instead of being in charge,
我就能当反对派
I can now be the vocal opposition,
事事都批评和纠缠主席
criticizing and badgering the president at every turn.
我认为你一定会做得很棒
I think you'll be really good at that.
我也觉得
Me, too.
我好像犯了一个很大的错误
I think I've made a huge mistake.
我也觉得
Me, too.
不敢相信你要到她的电话了
Can't believe you got her number.
就是啊
I know, right?
如果这事成了
How amazing would it be if this worked out
我跟我妻子相识的故事
and the story of how I met my wife
就从你我在浴缸共浴开始  那会有多赞啊
started with you and me in the hot tub together.
为了你跟我好  还是把故事开端推后一点吧
Well, do us both a favor and start the story later.
随便了
Whatever.
我对这个妹子有很好的预感
I have a good feeling about this girl.
我们很投缘
Like, we really hit it off.
别再飞来飞去
Stop flying it around.
你会把无人机弄坏的
You're gonna break it.
那有什么所谓
Why do you care?
因为我们得把它还给那个神秘的漂亮妹子
Because we have to give it back to the beautiful mystery girl.
你看到她有多性感了吗
I mean, did you see how hot she was?
我想提"枪"上阵  跟她生娃
I want to get all up on that and start making babies!
我已经想好了第一次约会时
I know exactly what underwear
我要穿什么内裤
I'm gonna wear on our first date.
"国王的内裤"
None!